[Rachel]
Previously on Titans...
I lied.
I told you that Jericho
was dead
when I got to the church.
He died trying to save me
from his father.
You lying sack of shit!
-I'm out.
-I'm out, too.
He got a kid killed.
Who the fuck hides that?
You were there, too.
You played your part.
[grunts]
Rachel, what's happening?
[Rachel] Sorry, Donna.
Conner, no!
[cop grunts]
[Mercy]
We got a potential murderer
walking around out there,
with our technological
fingerprints all over him.
We gotta bring
Subject 13 in.
-We'll need your team.
-My pleasure.
I help people that others
have given up on.
-He cured me.
-From what?
A rare disease, although
the cure I administered
had unforeseen side effects.
[screaming]
-Hello.
-Hi.
I took advantage of Jericho
to get to your husband.
I've got nothing
but pain for you.
-Grayson!
-You killed him.
This isn't about me.
You still haven't accepted
your guilt.
[Slade] I sentence you
to live alone, Dick Grayson.
Forever knowing
that your Titans family
lives and breathes
somewhere out there
in the world,
but you can never be with them.
Not until you've paid
for your crime.
Excuse me, sir.
[grunts]
[cop 1 grunts] Down...
-[cop 3] Get on the ground!
-[cop 4]
On the ground, now!
[cop 3] Show me your hands.
[cop 4]
Hands behind your head.
[cops continue yelling]
[guard] Turn to your left.
Now to the right.
[scanner beeps]
[pop music playing
on car stereo]
We should play
more board games
as a family.
It's supposed to
promote bonding
and connection.
And it's fun.
There's one
I read about online,
something about a penguin
eating a fish.
I hate fish.
Well, you don't
have to eat it.
It's a game.
It's make-believe.
Can we play a vegan
make-believe game?
I could use
a little help.
They don't like fish.
Well,
I don't like monogamy,
but I'm here, aren't I?
We're playing
a board game, tonight.
No dietary exemptions allowed.
[line ringing]
[console beeps]
Walter.
You're talking to everyone.
Hi, everyone.
There's been a development.
Subject 13's popped back
in our radar.
He's in the city.
Thought you would like to know.
Put a team together.
I was thinking
you would say that.
Say goodbye now.
-[cell phone beeps]
-Goodbye--
Game night's cancelled.
[breathing heavily]
[Krypto barks softly]
[Krypto whimpers]
[Conner] Look, buddy.
It's not safe for you
to be around me anymore.
[barks]
No, it's true.
Okay, sooner or later,
they're gonna find me.
You shouldn't be around
when that happens.
You might get hurt.
[Krypto whimpers]
You didn't do anything wrong.
Okay?
I did.
[barks, whines]
Go on, Krypto.
Get out of here.
[Krypto whining softly]
I said get the hell
out of here,
you stupid mutt!
Go!
[Krypto whimpering]
[guard] One call each.
Two minutes max.
Use it or lose it.
[inmates talking indistinctly]
[keyboard clacking]
Detective, huh?
I applied to the PD.
Got red-flagged
on the MMPI.
"I sometimes think of things
too horrible to speak of"?
Uh, that's a fucking
affirmative, Madam
Test Administrator.
Then spent four years
at Lyon County
until the bastards
finally realized they were
wasting my potential.
Welcome to Len Armstrong's
list of personal grievances.
I bet you got your own
with that cop-hating PD
who railroaded you
into a guilty plea.
Bullshit, if you ask me.
I wanted to plead guilty.
[scoffs] Sure.
Squeeze it down to 20 years
instead of 30.
Got what I deserve.
Goddamn prosecutors.
Always hit you
when you're down.
Don't worry. We take care
of our own here.
Welcome to the west wing.
No rose garden out back,
but you got your privacy.
Keep you tucked away
from the crazy.
Rent's free.
Just give me a heads-up
on shit before it hits the fan.
Eyes and ears out
in the yard.
You know the dealio.
Yeah. Not for me.
You'll wanna rethink that.
Gen pop's no place
for a guy who wore a badge.
Sorry. I'm out
of the business
of helping people.
Okay.
[scoffing]
Detour time.
[chuckles]
[Len clears throat]
Brought you someone new
to play with.
Enjoy...
Detective.
[inmates speaking Spanish]
[people clamoring on video]
[reporter] Witnesses say
that the young man
was immune to police gunfire.
San Francisco PD has issued
a $50,000 reward
for information
leading to his arrest.
[line ringing]
[Dick]
This is Dick Grayson.
I can't take your call
right now.
Leave a message.
Dick, it's me again.
[stammers] I know
I screwed things up
really bad, man, but...
And I get why maybe you don't
want to talk to me.
But please, call me back.
[sighs]
[automated voice]
Security alert, zone two.
Downstairs entry.
Hello. Who's there?
[Krypto barks]
Krypto.
Hey, Dick. I know we're not
exactly on chatty terms,
but Rachel went AWOL
before our flight to Chicago.
So...
I'm still in the city.
I figure she'll turn up
when she runs out of cash,
but... I'm really
starting to get worried.
Just call me back, okay?
Fuck!
[employee] Here you go, dear.
There you go.
-[Rachel] Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[cell phone vibrating]
Do you think
these are organic?
[sighs]
We've gotta die of something.
[indistinct conversations]
Ow!
It's my dead pile.
[inmate] Working hard,
or hardly working?
Yeah, it's your play, man.
[Santos] All right.
[gate buzzing]
Yo, we got a problem?
Nope.
Hey.
So, what's up?
You keeping an eye on us?
Just minding my own business.
Yeah, so am I.
Hey! Best buds already.
Melts my heart.
Mind if I cut in?
Used to be MS-13 littered
this place with corpses.
Now it's these Corto Maltese.
Last month,
I had to deport seven of 'em.
Got a punctured lung
as a parting gift.
Sorry for throwing you in
with animals,
but I had to make a point.
Now, let's bypass the bullshit
and get down to business.
Okay.
So, no hard feelings?
Sure.
Believe me, I had your back.
Let me get that single
ready for you.
Move you out of the jungle.
Hey.
What's up?
Don't.
I'm not helping you.
-You said we were good.
-We are.
And I'm not helping you...
or anybody. It's not personal.
You fucking with me again?
No.
So you wanna be in there?
That's right.
You know what happens
to the cop who's in cahoots
with the boss?
Nothing good. [laughs]
Enjoy your stay, kid.
[inmates grunting and groaning]
[inmate exclaims and gasps]
-Rent is due, motherfucker!
-We don't want any problems!
Too late!
You left the family.
They'll slice you up
when you get home.
Or we'll slice you up now.
Or you pay the rent.
Your call.
We'll do it.
-Rafi, no!
-Shut the fuck up.
-I said we'll do it. Who?
-[groaning] Rafi.
Your new celly. The cop.
-Why him?
-'Cause he's a cop,
motherfucker!
You saw him in the yard.
He's down with the guards.
Twelve hours, puto.
[barks]
Great. Dumbest dog ever.
He can ring a doorbell
with his nose.
I've seen dumber.
-[barks]
-Stay away from me.
What you did to those cops...
You messed things up
for a lot of people,
including me.
I think I deserve an answer.
What the hell happened?
When you invited me
to be a Titan,
I told you what I was.
But you didn't listen
'cause that's not what
you wanted to hear.
You're right.
I didn't listen.
Being a Titan
isn't about being perfect.
I...
I killed a guy once.
And I clawed him to pieces.
So, maybe we should both
be locked up.
What we do...
Other people count on us
to help them.
Well, they shouldn't.
[barking]
[tires squeal]
You gotta get
out of here. Now!
No, no, no!
Do you really want
to hurt somebody else?
-[Krypto continues barking]
-[soldier] Move, move!
Come on, now!
Come on.
[soldier] Move, move!
[woman scoffs]
Mmm. Mmm,
these lemon things
are delicious.
They get all their food
from the Ritz Carlton
down the street.
Leftovers from big
muckity-muck conventions.
Bon appetit.
So, what brings you
to this fine ding
establishment?
Sorry, that was...
Uh, you don't have
to answer that.
-Sorry.
-It's all right.
I left.
My family's fucked up.
Yeah, can't relate.
You look at
all these grown-ups,
and you...
You think
that they have the answers.
Then you find out
they just have no idea.
I think it's a test.
The longer we don't break free,
the dumber we are.
Mmm. Sixteen years.
That's like a D-minus for me.
Have you ever heard
of a Labord's chameleon?
Can't say I have.
It's a lizard species
in Madagascar.
The females lay their eggs
before the winter
and then all the adults
die before they hatch.
So, from the minute
you're born, no parents.
You're totally on your own.
Yeah. Only downside is,
your life span's
only five months.
And you're, uh,
green and scaly.
But... you're totally free,
all your life.
No rules, no bullshit.
No adults fucking you up.
[scoffs] We should
have been lizards.
Time to go.
You don't have to.
Mind your business, kid.
It's okay.
You disappear on me again,
I'll fucking kill you.
Why wait?
Fine.
[groans]
I'm not a kid.
[groaning]
[straining]
Please, don't kill me.
Please... Please...
[grunts]
[Rachel gasping]
[exclaims]
I'm sorry.
Being a lizard would be
considerably less freaky.
You're fucking awesome.
[snarling]
[panting]
Oh, shit.
[gargoyle growling]
[exclaiming and yelling]
-No! No! [screams]
-[gargoyle screeching]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
[dominos clacking]
[shiv scratching]
When's the escape?
I saw you looking
at the guards at the gate.
So, you ratted us out, huh?
If I did,
you'd all be in solitary.
If I can see what you're up to,
soon enough, they will.
The fucking snitch
giving us tips?
Just facts.
Four guards on the ground.
Two in the tower with M14s
with 20 rounds each.
-You got no chance.
-Yeah.
You're so smart, huh?
Why don't you tell us
how we're gonna stay alive?
I'd kill me.
[sighs]
I could fucking kill you.
Make it easier on all of us.
But that's not who I am.
We're not murders.
That's why we left
the Corto Maltese
and tried to go clean.
Immigration picked us up.
And they're gonna deport us.
At home, we're deserters,
just like in here.
So, the Corto Maltese
will slaughter us like pigs.
We have no choice
but to break out.
So, unless
you have real answers...
shut the fuck up.
You hungry?
You want something to eat?
Yeah.
Hey. You know they're gonna
keep coming after me, right?
Let them try.
This is my mess,
not yours.
This is what the Titans do.
We have each other's backs.
So, where are they?
The other Titans.
You know what,
maybe I should do
what Dick wanted me to do
in the first place.
Call in the big guns.
We're gonna use guns?
No, it's just a metaphor.
Calling Bruce Wayne.
[automated voice]
Zone six, unauthorized access.
What's that?
Zone six is the roof.
[soldier 1] Hurry, now!
Everybody down on the floor!
[soldier 2] Stay where you are!
-[soldier 1] Hands,
let me see your hands!
-[soldier 2] Don't move!
[barking]
[soldier 3] Target ID'd.
[Mercy]
Bring Subject 13 in alive.
Kill the other one.
[continues barking]
[soldier 1]
Shut that damn dog up!
[soldier groans]
[soldier 2] Bag him!
[Krypto whimpers]
[soldiers grunt]
[both grunting]
[soldier grunting and yelling]
Ha! Ha! Oh!
[soldier yelling]
[grunting]
[growls]
Change of plan,
tranquilizers only.
-[Gar growling over tablet]
-Bring the tiger in alive.
[Gar snarling and growling]
Screw this. I'm switching
to Kryptonite bullets.
No! No Kryptonite!
[soldier] Tranqs!
[Gar groans]
No.
[whines]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
Stop!
It's okay.
I'm not here to hurt you.
Who are you?
My name is Mercy Graves,
I work with Eve Watson.
Eve?
Is she here?
No, she sent me instead.
[Gar wheezing]
It's okay.
It's just tranquilizers
to calm him.
I'm here to help you.
That's not what it feels like.
Do you want to hurt me?
I'm not sure.
Did you want to hurt
those police officers?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
These are not...
easy questions, Conner.
Let us help you.
After all, we created you.
We can fix you.
"Fix"?
What's happening to you,
it's our fault.
An imbalance
we didn't consider,
but now that we understand it,
we can stop it.
All you have to do...
is come home.
[sighs]
[door unlocks]
What is this place?
I've brought someone
who can help us.
[indistinct conversations]
Hey, hey.
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
We've been here all morning.
-I'm bored.
-Well, bored's
better than dead.
Take a nap.
I'm not tired.
Neither are they.
We stick together
till tonight.
It's a suicide mission.
We're gonna make it.
Will you shut the fuck up,
all of you?
[Luis] It's not suicide.
You think
we can't beat the guards
with their guns,
but we can.
You know why?
Alazul.
You know Alazul?
In our village,
Alazul is our hero.
He lives between the moon
and the stars.
And in the time
of greatest need,
he flies down and saves you.
A bird that comes in the night
and saves people?
Yes.
He's gonna save us tonight...
and we'll be free.
Okay, Luis...
there's no Alazul.
Yes, there is.
[Dick] Then why are you here?
The gangs that came after you,
Immigration
that came after you.
This bird's
supposed to save you?
Where the hell has he been?
Huh?
He's real.
And tonight...
he's gonna save us.
You'll see.
[Walter]
Subject 13 is in stasis.
[Mercy] I'll call Mr. Luthor
to get instructions
on recalibration.
How's our other guest?
Well, I'd like to say
all bark and no bite,
but I wouldn't put
money on it.
[keypad beeping]
Mr. Logan. I'm Mercy Graves.
It's an honor to meet you.
Can I interest you
in something else to eat?
Grass-fed ribeye?
Chia pudding?
Name anything you'd like.
How about
letting me out of here?
I'm afraid
that's not available
on DoorDash.
[Gar chuckles]
What have you done
to Conner?
Exactly as he wanted.
We didn't force him
to come back.
It was his choice.
[scoffs]
Yeah, 'cause you guys
are all about
the free will here.
Loving mine, by the way.
My apologies
for any discomfort.
We just wanted
to contain your transformation
to ensure
we had the opportunity to talk.
[exhales] Let me guess,
you guys can "fix" me, too.
No.
But I could help you.
I could offer you
what Niles Caulder never did.
Dr. Caulder
and CADMUS Industries
have crossed paths
from time to time.
He's a brilliant man.
Though,
not entirely altruistic,
no matter how he wishes
to appear.
He saved you.
Gave you the gift of life,
but only as it suited
his needs.
His purpose.
Did he ever ask you
what you want,
for yourself?
Has anyone?
Or do they just
string you along...
using you for their own ends,
with little concern for you
or your welfare?
CADMUS will focus on you.
Help you explore your powers
to their fullest.
Help you be...
everything you want to be.
What I wanna be is a Titan.
[siren wailing in distance]
[woman]
I was out here last night,
but it was too dark to see.
[police siren chirps]
Dick, I need you
to call me back.
[exhales]
I tracked Rachel down
to a soup kitchen.
Look, she's not just missing.
It's worse.
[gate buzzing]
Give me my points!
Okay, that's it.
Get inside, now.
Now, now.
Get in.
[Luis] Hey, hey! Santos.
[alarm blaring]
[indistinct announcement
over PA]
[inmates clamoring]
Move! Go!
Get out of the fucking way!
Call a medic.
Too late.
[praying in Spanish]
[guard] Lockdown...
until your transport tonight.
Warden's orders.
[door locks]
If you say
we should have killed you,
I'll break your fucking face.
Don't go through
with this tonight.
[scoffs]
Now you fucking care?
With Santos,
you had no chance.
Without him...
Santos being killed...
that's your sign saying,
don't do this.
If you can't see that,
you're blind.
I'm blind?
If God wants me dead,
then it'll be my time.
But if I'm
still alive tomorrow,
then that's my sign.
And it means that I'm exactly
where I'm supposed to be.
Now, he's giving me
a chance...
to be something else.
Maybe you're the one
who's blind.
[exhales]
[door unlocks]
[door opening]
Rise and shine, boys.
It's 6:00 a.m.
Say goodbye to America.
Hope you had a nice stay.
[handcuffs clicking]
[guard] Sit tight.
All right,
we just need to get
the receiver's signature
on the transport manifesto.
[handcuffs clicking]
All right, load 'em up.
[guard] Time to go, gentlemen.
-On your feet.
-[door creaking]
Now.
[guards grunt]
[moans]
[all grunt]
[grunts]
[blows landing]
[all grunt]
[Dick] Go.
-[gate buzzing]
-[alarm blaring]
[gunfire continues]
[groans]
[Len grunts] Hey.
-Cuff him!
-[guard] Get on the ground.
[Dick groans]
The man who won't help anyone.
[wind whistling]
[traffic in distance]
I spoke to Mr. Luthor.
There have been some changes
regarding Subject 13
and Project Rakshasa.
With all due respect,
Ms. Graves,
I don't answer to you.
Well,
that's one of the changes.
Now you do.
[Walter] What do we do
about him?
[Mercy] He says
he wants to be a Titan,
reunited with his team.
I think it's an excellent idea.
[Wicked Witch laughing on TV]