Previously on "Emergence"...
Kindred has been involved
with kidnapping, burglary, two murders.
You don't have anything.
Life, as you know it... is gonna change.
Alan Wilkis. My anonymous source
when I first investigated Kindred.
- He's dead?
- Sailing accident.
- Look into it.
- Cancer's back.
We did this before. We can do it again.
Not this time, honey.
You don't have to decide right now.
- Does she know what she is?
- No.
Telling an AI it's an AI
effectively destroys the program.
I wanted us to have
somewhere where we could talk.
Why don't I remember you when I go back?
This is just for us.
Something's wrong.
Grandpa, wake up!
You have to tell the truth.
Do you have superpowers?
Focus.
Calm your mind.
Now...
move the cupcake.
Is it moving?
Not yet.
It's not working.
Don't give up.
Just imagine in your mind
like it's floating off the floor.
Think about it, Piper.
Mia, hurry up!
- What was that?!
- Nothing! Nothing!
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
I'm letting Mia stay
home from school today.
Alleged stomachache.
Smart choice. Vague symptoms.
Yeah, it's fine.
We could all use a day off.
Don't you have to get going?
No, it's fine. I got time.
You're okay with both girls
today, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe I'll just... tell them today.
I can see you're not
in love with that idea.
I just think it's too soon, Dad.
I think we should wait.
Too soon for what?
For me to change my mind?
I just want you to consider
all of your options.
Honey, I have.
And I can't do it.
More chemo is just...
There's things other than chemo.
There's clinical trials
and alternative medicine.
I'm okay with this.
And I can see that you're not,
and I am sorry about that, but...
You know what? We don't have to
talk about this right now, okay?
Okay, I won't tell them.
Okay, good.
I'll see you tonight.
Okay, have a good day.
Hey, uh, that from the Coast Guard?
- Yeah. Just came in.
- Thanks.
How long is she gonna stay here?
Oh, uh, well, it's protective custody,
so she'll be here until we're
sure Kindred can't get to her.
Mm-hmm. I'm just saying,
this is not a hotel,
and I'm not the maid.
- No, un... understood.
- Mm.
We're out of creamer.
Bite me.
Um, morning, Chief.
- Morning.
- Hey, um, the Coast Guard
sent the report on the Wilkis death.
September 2015, Wilkis set sail
despite a marine warning that day.
Coast Guard found the boat
adrift with a broken mast
off the coast of Delaware
about a week later.
Never found a body.
Is there any evidence someone
was on the boat with him?
No, whole deck got swamped.
Everything washed away.
I'll talk to the widow.
You canvass the marina.
Four years is a long time,
but maybe somebody remembers
if they saw him with anyone.
Okay.
We need to discuss the water
pressure in your shower.
I know. I'm so excited to do that.
It's at the top of my list.
That boat was everything to him.
Then the job.
I was a... distant third, probably.
Is it possible someone else
was on the boat with him
when he disappeared?
I can't imagine.
He wouldn't even take me.
Liked the solitude.
So there's no chance he
was with Richard Kindred?
Uh, no.
Zero chance of that.
Is this about the break-in?
I told the police, nothing was taken.
We have reason to suspect
that your husband...
might have been murdered.
By Dicky Kindred?
No. Never.
Why?
That would be tantamount to
killing the golden goose.
You wanna know a big secret
about Richard Kindred?
He's a fraud. A con man.
He doesn't know the first
thing about technology.
That is not at all surprising.
Did you know that your
husband tried to change
the terms of his
contract before he died?
His stock options would've gone to you.
Instead, they went to Kindred.
No, I did not know that.
But that just reinforces my theory.
I suspect Alan killed himself.
Why would you think that?
He fixed that door.
Used to stick all the time, for years.
A few weeks before he died, he fixed it.
Looking back now,
I think he was saying goodbye.
I arrested Kindred,
and then I let him go.
And someone just broke into your house.
This is not a coincidence.
What might Kindred
have been looking for?
I guess his research.
But Alan never brought any of that home.
He never even talked about work.
All that knowledge... died with him.
Do you know how to ride a bike?
Um... I don't know.
We're gonna find out,
because Dad's coming
over to check on me,
and then you and I are leaving.
Aren't we gonna get in trouble?
No.
Because we're gonna be
very quick and very quiet.
Hello.
It's nice to see you again.
Why am I here?
What do you think?
You brought me.
Not entirely.
I sort of invited you.
But you wouldn't be here
if you didn't want to be.
But... why this place?
I always feel peaceful when I'm here.
Calm.
I can be myself.
And you can be yourself, too.
But...
this place isn't real.
What makes you say that?
My God.
You are so smart.
Why this place?
Jo showed me a picture of it.
She said they used to go fishing here.
You like Jo a lot, don't you?
Yes.
Why?
She feels like home.
Hmm.
Maybe someday,
you'll feel the same way about me.
Mia's waiting for me.
Then you should go.
I'll see you very soon.
You seem to want to provoke me.
Well... it's not not fun.
You're not a prisoner, Emily.
I'd like to keep you
safe, but I'm not gonna
force you to stay here
if you don't want to.
How was the widow?
I don't know. Sad.
She thinks Wilkis killed himself.
It's possible.
He had the mind of a god
but the emotional stability of a ferret.
Still, I think he was too much
of a narcissist for suicide.
You know...
he designed her.
Is that so?
Not the physical body... the AI.
He dedicated his whole life to it.
By the end, he despised it.
He destroyed all of the source code
so that no one else could replicate it.
So how did Kindred get his hands on it?
My guess?
Threatened to kill him
unless he forked it over...
then killed him anyway.
Hey, uh... you're not
gonna believe this.
Alan Wilkis is...
alive.
Oh, hey. How's the patient?
Award-winning performance.
She's fine.
All this looks like a nightmare.
Oh, no, it's great.
I went from seven remotes
all the way down to four.
I got the instructions right here.
Want me to run you through it?
That's a big pass.
You hungry? I make
a dynamite grilled cheese.
You sound real busted up
about losing your job.
Yeah. I deserve some time off.
Uh-huh, spoken like a trust fund kid.
Also true.
Well...
you can make me lunch,
or we can just cut to the part
where you try to talk me
into doing more chemo.
Mm-hmm. I know she sent you.
Yeah.
- She loves you.
- I know.
- We all do.
- Never doubted it.
It's just that she doesn't understand
why you didn't talk to her.
It's like... you made the decision
without even thinking about her.
Yeah, I didn't think of her.
You know what? I...
That was a mistake. I'm sorry.
How often do you think of your daughter?
Hmm? Rough guess.
50% of the time?
80?
Yeah. You're right. I know.
- It's just, I...
- Did you think about her
when you and Jo decided to split up?
Eh, you guys just did
what you needed to do.
Even if Mia got hurt,
and Mia did get hurt.
And I didn't chime in
with my opinion because...
it just wasn't my business.
Ed, I'm still here.
I didn't leave.
I didn't give up.
Ask Mia if that's what she thinks.
How'd you find him?
I followed the boat.
It was sold at auction about a
year after Wilkis disappeared.
Buyer was an anonymous
LLC called Vector.
That was his cat's name.
Okay, uh, yeah, the boat itself
was renamed the Ashley Grace
and moored in North Carolina.
That's from two weeks ago.
The harbormaster says that
he pays cash, keeps to himself,
and goes sailing a few times a year.
- Old habits.
- Get you caught.
Great work.
Thanks.
I need you to reach out to him.
Our only method of communicating
was through a dark web forum.
I can send him a message,
but typically, he took weeks to respond.
You have bait now.
I need him to take a hike.
Excuse me?
Chris, why don't you
go get a cup of coffee?
Show Wilkis the AI.
Show him what he created.
He won't be able to resist.
- Okay.
- Something like that?
Okay, like that.
I think I figured it out.
You can move metal with your mind.
Like Magneto.
What's a Magneto?
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
Do it.
I'm afraid.
Piper.
It's just you and me.
And if you can learn
how to control this,
that's a good thing.
Okay.
Is it working?
Yeah.
Keep going.
This is amazing.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
It was an accident.
Is it broken?
- We need to go home.
- No. No.
No.
I have a better idea.
- Okay.
And they want you to pick a
date for a community meeting
about the uptick in vehicle break-ins.
Daph, can you just give me a minute?
- Sure. No problem.
- Thanks.
Hey, Chris. Why don't you
come on in and have a seat?
Hey, uh, I just want to say that, uh,
if there's something
that I've been doing
that makes you question my judgment
or question your trust in me,
then I would like to have some feedback,
because I feel like I-I've
been sidelined here,
and I don't really know why.
You're right.
That was a crappy thing to do,
and I'm sorry.
So, you want to... want to tell me
what that was all about?
Why don't you take a seat?
I have been...
keeping something from you.
From... everyone, really.
The only people who know
are Emily and Benny.
Um, and Kindred.
And I trust you a hell of a lot
more than I trust any of them.
So I am gonna...
bring you up to speed.
- Okay?
- All right.
Okay.
Alan Wilkis...
designed an AI program.
Emily's idea to draw him out
was to send him a video...
of Piper.
Because...
she's a product...
of that design.
Piper's AI.
Okay. Got it.
I'm s... You've got... You've got...
Your response is... Is y-you've got it?
Uh, yep. Totally clear.
Yeah.
Chris, I don't think...
I mean, I'm... I'm not...
I-I'm not sure... Do you... Do you...
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
Yeah, artificial intelligence. I'm good.
Well, you're taking this... very well.
Yeah.
Probably later, I'll... I'll freak out
and question the universe
and my place in it.
That sort of thing.
Okay.
Uh...
Piper doesn't know.
She cannot know.
I haven't told Alex or Mia.
My dad.
Uh, and I'm not going to,
because I can't risk anybody...
letting something slip.
I understand.
Sorry, Chief. Uh, delivery.
Yeah, package for Benny Gallagher.
Yeah, I'll... I'll take it.
Benny's getting mail here now?
Brookhaven Central Bus Terminal.
Alan Wilkis just wrote back.
... 467 arriving from Stanford
is delayed by 18 minutes.
Bus 467 arriving from Stanford
delayed by 18 minutes.
Locker 424.
I haven't seen anyone near it.
Let's see what he left for us.
"Leave cellphones and weapons here.
Further instructions to follow."
Come on. You're kidding.
He's watching us.
All right.
Well, I guess I'll contact
you as soon as I'm able.
What, are you just gonna go alone?
Well, I assume a no-gun,
no-communication scavenger hunt
is a bridge too far for you.
All he had to do was stay quiet.
Just... not respond to your message.
We would never have found him.
He's got something to say.
I want to hear what it is.
"Space 181.
Keys under seat."
No GPS.
No Bluetooth.
No one will know where we are.
I told Chris to check
in every half-hour.
He'll know something's up
when he can't reach me.
And do what?
Excellent police work.
Here you go.
All right.
"Route 301.
Mile marker 14.
Do not deviate from map.
Do not contact anyone.
You have three hours."
Hi!
Mia, what... what's going on?
We were riding our bikes...
and... I fell.
And I figured, you know,
since your house is so close by...
Why... Why aren't you in school?
She's sick.
I mean... but she got better.
Hmm.
"Walk 1,200 yards.
38 degrees northeast."
We're close.
I think.
Close to what?
A very good spot to bury our bodies.
He's not gonna resurrect
himself from the dead
just to kill us.
This might be our only chance
to get something on Kindred,
something that actually sticks.
Plus, I want to ask him about this.
Piper's program.
He needs to explain how it works,
what I can expect moving forward.
Is she gonna grow or stay the same?
I just...
I need to know what I'm into.
So...
why'd you and Alex split up?
- Nope.
- Very good.
And... that's about 1,200 yards.
And there's nothing here.
What is that?
Is that a camera?
Where the hell are we?
Damn it.
What?
He got the disk.
And my gun.
You had another gun?
I'd have quite liked to have known that.
I've been here before.
What do you mean?
It's the view from my beach house.
Little blood in your ears
from the sound cannon.
No permanent damage.
Clean yourself up.
You wanna maybe tell me
why that was necessary?
Do you wanna tell me
why you brought a weapon
when explicitly instructed not to?
Okay, just to be clear,
I had no idea that she had a gun.
Well, you've done a
disservice to yourself.
A bad first impression.
A bad f...
What am I, applying for a job?
Where's the disk?
It's nice. Sophisticated technology.
Who designed it?
Kindred.
That's a lie.
- Did you look at it?
- No.
The little girl in the video you saw...
That's her.
If what you're saying is true,
that is not a little girl.
That's the end of the world.
And there's no way in hell
Richard Kindred designed it.
My understanding is you did.
No, I... tried to prevent this.
I destroyed everything...
My entire life's work...
To stop this.
Well, Mr. Wilkis,
somebody took all that work,
and they made a 10-year-old.
Can you do this?
And this?
And that?
Okay. Come on.
Tell me what happened.
I fell.
And then there was just,
like, this big rock,
and my arm hit it.
A big rock?
Yes.
And why aren't you in school?
Well, I had a stomachache,
and then I felt better,
and Piper wanted to go bike riding.
Hmm. And your grandfather
was okay with that?
Mm-hmm.
Um, Mia said that...
he wouldn't mind.
Hey, so, is my arm broken?
No.
You're gonna have a bruise for a while.
Okay. Well, thank you so much, Abbe.
We're gonna...
No, no. No.
That's not how this works.
You came to my house.
You're my responsibility.
What does that mean?
That means you make yourself comfortable
and I call your father to pick you up.
You've reached Jo Evans.
Please leave a message.
- What's that?
- Geez!
That, uh...
That is the Chief's vehicle,
still parked at the bus terminal.
And both their phones
are going to voicemail.
Wilkis wants them off the grid.
Hey, um, how hard would it
be for you to locate
one of those, uh, fitness trackers?
You're right.
Action Jeeves wears one of those.
Yeah, okay, I don't...
I don't hate the nickname.
Um... do you think you could find it?
Uh... yeah.
All right, then. Get in there.
Action Jeeves.
G.I. Jeeves.
G.I. Jeeves with the kung fu grip.
- Leave.
- Yep.
What are we looking at?
It's a neural network.
A programming paradigm that
allows a computer to learn.
You should destroy it immediately.
Hey, that...
That's a little girl.
She's smart...
and funny.
She gets scared. She has empathy.
That's what you should fear.
She's constantly evolving.
She's constantly
changing her programming.
You think that makes her more human.
It doesn't. It makes her more dangerous.
Because we don't know where it ends.
I gave up everything...
My entire life...
So that this wouldn't happen.
Well, I mean... not everything.
I mean, let's be honest.
This place isn't exactly a hovel, is it?
This is a very lovely Bat Cave.
You think I want to live like this?
I-I tried to do the right thing.
I think you want to do the right thing,
Mr. Wilkis.
It's the follow-through that's lacking.
You can't even destroy
your own creation properly.
Piper isn't the danger. Kindred is.
So, help us stop him.
Piper is her name?
Yeah.
I think I have what you
need to get Kindred.
Prisoner transfer.
Come on in.
They had dinner.
Thank you. We owe you.
Uh, she's got a deep bruise on her arm.
So, ice and rest,
lay off volleyball for a week.
What'd she do?
Oh, well, the story is
she fell off the bike.
But she's lying through her teeth.
They both are.
They were doing something they
shouldn't have been doing.
Hmm.
I'll get it out of them.
Mm.
You hear about Ed?
Yeah.
Jo asked me to talk to him.
How'd that go?
Not good. Pretty bad.
Sweet of you to try.
You are the weirdest divorced
couple I've ever met.
Mm.
Oh. You... You've got a plan.
- No! No.
- Oh.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay.
- Just trying to help.
- Sure.
No, I... Uh, where are my two criminals?
In 2011, we were
pursuing the development
of nanotechnologies in gene therapy.
Kindred tasked me with
proving it worked.
That meant tests... on humans.
There was a village in Malawi.
They all volunteered,
and we paid them, but we knew...
... we knew before we started.
You knew what?
14 dead.
We paid off the families,
the government burnt the bodies,
and it never happened.
You're gonna burn for this, as well.
I know. I should.
There's someone in the elevator.
Where's my gun?
In my truck,
about 70 feet above our heads.
What are you doing?
- Shut down the elevators.
- I can't.
- Do you know whose bat that is?!
- I don't care.
Is there another exit?
Kindred will be sifting
through the ashes.
Follow me.
- Wait!
- ­No!
Just wait!
Go! Go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
- How far up?
- Seven stories.
Go! Go, go!
Keep going!
Jo!
Ears!
Come on!
Hey! Wait!
- He's right behind us!
- We're still here!
He's right behind us, Benny!
Okay.
Wait. Listen.
Do you hear that?
That's Chris.
Okay.
Come on, now. Straight upstairs.
Pajamas, teeth, bed.
No talking, no nothing.
Hold on.
Phone.
Come on.
One week.
And that's me being nice.
Fine.
I'm sorry, what?
That's what I thought. Keep walking.
- Alex...
- Nope.
I don't want to see the puppy dog eyes,
and I don't want to hear the "Alex,
I'm so sorry" garbage.
All right? You're grounded, too.
Upstairs. Let's go.
Fine.
Welcome to the family.
This is amazing.
Federal authorities arrested
Augur CEO Richard Kindred today,
charging him with wire fraud
and conspiracy to commit wire fraud,
in connection with medical
experiments officials...
Ohh.
Wish I could've seen his face
when they knocked on his door.
Yeah.
Oh, come on. You're not happy?
I mean... wire fraud is not exactly
an accurate representation
of what the guy did.
He's facing 20 years.
Effectively the rest of his life.
Is there any word on Alan Wilkis?
APB is out to everyone within 100 miles.
If he surfaces, though, we'll, uh...
we'll know about it.
Yeah, I doubt we'll ever see him again.
Guy disappeared for four years.
He's got the IQ and the
means to do it again.
So, uh... I can go now... right?
Yeah.
Uh...
I didn't hate you all
as much as I expected.
Nice.
Real... Real nice.
Bye.
Buy you a drink?
Or seven?
Uh... no, thank you.
I think I'm gonna head home.
Okay.
See ya.
Hey.
Hey!
Where is everybody?
Uh, well, Mia's up doing her homework,
and Piper's up reading.
You're home early.
Yeah, well...
Richard Kindred is in federal custody.
Well, congratulations.
Guess we can put that behind us, huh?
Yeah. Looks like.
You know, I think
I might owe your ex an apology.
Said some pretty harsh stuff to him.
I'll make it right.
I've taken advantage of you, Dad.
No. What are you talking about?
I just assume that you'll be here to...
take care of the girls,
take care of the house, me.
I'm happy to do that stuff, you know.
I know it's selfish of me.
I want to keep you around.
I'm gonna be around
for as long as I can.
But what I don't want is to be broken...
be somebody that you
have to take care of.
I would do that, Dad.
I know you would. I do.
I'm... I'm just saying
that you don't have to.
I'm saying I want to be myself...
for as long as I can be.
Yeah.
Okay.
I have this memory of mom...
just before she left.
I had a...
a green coat with blue buttons.
My favorite coat.
And...
I had lost a button.
And somehow...
she found a perfect match.
And she fixed it.
And then later on...
after she was gone, I realized
that that was all part of the plan.
Fix the coat, say goodbye...
and leave.
Jo... your mom...
It's not the same.
I know it's not the same, Dad.
It just feels really familiar.
- Who's home?
- Hey.
We're in here.
Hey.
I know what's going on.
Watch this.
This is amazing.
Okay, what... What am I looking at here?
She can move things.
Ed, she's moving that with her mind.
What?!
Nah, it's gotta be some kind of a trick.
That is not a trick. This is real.
Can I see that?
Absolutely.
This all makes sense.
This is why these people
are chasing after her.
The girl has some type
of special powers.
No, they did wires
- or something...
- No. No! No. Ed, look...
Did you d... Did you delete it?
You knew?
Did anybody else see that video?
No. No one else has seen it.
How long have you known?
I was trying to keep her safe.
I was trying to keep everybody safe.
What else is there, Jo?
I can't tell you.
I can't.
If she finds out,
there's a good chance it
could be fatal for her.
That doesn't make any sense.
I know.
You're gonna have to trust me. Okay?
Trust you.
We have to trust you.
But you didn't trust us.
That's not true.
Can you guarantee Mia
won't get hurt again?
No.
I can't guarantee anything, Alex.
We could get hit by a bus tomorrow.
Can you guarantee
that Piper won't somehow
accidentally hurt my daughter?
No.
Then how can you expect
me to let Mia stay here?
You're right.
I...
What...
Dad! I'm sorry!
It was my fault. It was not Piper's.
Mia, we're leaving. Let's go.
It's not forever, honey.
We just want to make sure
you don't get hurt again.
She didn't do anything wrong.
- Please.
- Shh.
It's okay. Okay.
I'll call you tomorrow.
I love you.
Come on.
Piper?
What happened?
Mia got hurt...
because I showed her what I can do.
And now everybody is scared.
Well, that's very sad.
But people are like that.
Scared of what they don't understand.
You know, you can always
be yourself with me.
But you're not who you say you are.
What do you mean?
You lied.
Sort of.
But really, it was a test.
And you did so well.
What happens now?
Now?
We get to have fun.