[BELL CLANGING]
[SEA GULLS SQUAWKING]
♪♪
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[SAFETY PIN SCRAPES]
[SEA GULL SQUAWKING]
[HUMMING STOPS]
♪♪
[PROJECTILE WHISTLING,
CRASH IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
MIA: Mom? What was that?
Yeah, hold on.
- ED: Power's out.
- Yeah.
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
[CELLPHONE BUZZES]
Yeah, I see it.
I'm on my way.
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
I got to get dressed and go in to work.
You guys should go back to bed.
Can I come?
Sure can't. Bed.
- What is it?
- I'll call you.
Come on.
♪♪
[SIRENS WAIL]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[RADIO CHATTER]
♪♪
CHRIS: Hey, Chief.
JO: What do we got?
We're thinking it's a
mid-sized private jet.
10-passenger, tops.
FAA's trying to figure out who it was.
Uh, closest airport's Mattituck,
and they're not missing anybody.
And then the PSEG's
looking into the blackout.
They think the... the plane
might have clipped one of their lines.
Couldn't explain why
my cellphone stopped working, though.
Well, uh, there's a cell tower
about a mile away,
so the telecom company's
already investigating.
Alright. Set up a perimeter.
Start canvassing for witnesses.
I'll get Parks to shut down the beach.
You got it.
Good work.
[WAVES CRASHING]
♪♪
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Kind of cold out here.
You want to maybe borrow my coat?
CHRIS: Chief.
Every... Everything alright, or...?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
I'm just talking to my new friend here.
Hey.
You like that movie?
I love it.
You know who my favorite character is?
Woody.
♪♪
You see this right here?
Yeah, I'm like Woody.
Okay?
So I can help you.
Alright?
Why don't you come here?
It's okay.
Come on.
Ooh! Okay.
Okay.
Was she on the plane?
I don't know.
Can I get a paramedic over here?
Paramedic!
We just need to have them
look you over, okay?
Make sure you're not hurt.
So, can you let go of me for one second?
- No?
- NTSB is here.
They're saying they need
to clear everybody out.
Alright, uh, yeah, I'll handle it.
Go ahead.
Okay, um, can you just have someone
take my car by the hospital later?
Thanks.
Alright, we're gonna go together.
I'm coming with you. Come on.
ABBY: Good news is
she's physically fine.
No contusions, no head trauma,
not even a paper cut.
Bad news is she says she
doesn't remember anything.
She doesn't know her name,
doesn't know where she's from.
You think that's real?
I sent her for a head CT,
but my guess is that it's
dissociative amnesia.
Something traumatic happened,
and her brain is protecting itself.
What, something traumatic
like a plane crash?
I don't see how that's possible.
She doesn't have a scratch on her.
There she is!
Wasn't so scary, was it?
MAN: Oh, she did great.
Super brave.
Thanks.
Well, everything looks great.
You are a perfectly healthy girl.
Can I go home?
I would love that.
Where's home?
[TELEPHONE RINGS IN DISTANCE]
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER P.A.]
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
That's a great choice.
Maybe Jo can stay with you
until you fall asleep, hmm?
Yeah.
I can absolutely do that.
I'm hoping the memory will come back
in the next day or so.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Yeah.
[SIREN WAILS IN DISTANCE]
[SIGHS]
Oh, I, uh,
stopped by the vending machine
while they were looking
inside your head.
You know candy?
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Okay.
It's good to know you remember
the really important stuff.
Let's see.
What color?
Let me see.
Guess.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Red.
Yellow.
Again?
Mnh. Green.
Ugh. Not fair.
It's not my fault that
you're bad at this game.
[CANDY PIECES RATTLE]
Red. I mean purple. Purple.
Okay, I'm gonna give this to you...
- Yes!
- ... this one time.
But you really need to practice, okay,
- 'cause you're terrible at this.
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
Can we do another one?
Um, you know what?
You can practice by yourself,
but don't have too many,
and I will be right back.
Okay? Stay here.
- Doctor, you are interfering...
- ABBY: You don't have any right...
- ... with a federal investigation.
- ... to her private medical files!
What is this?
They're demanding to speak with her
- and look at her chart.
- Okay.
Hi. I'm Police Chief Jo Evans.
Who are you?
Sir, you will be in
federal lockup tonight
if you don't get out of my way.
Let's see how that goes for you.
NTSB doesn't have arrest authority.
I do.
Escort these men out of here.
Listen, why don't we just
go down to the waiting room,
and then you guys can tell
me what the hell's going on.
- Okay?
- ABBY: She's gone!
♪♪
- JO: Station teams at every exit.
- This is a code yellow.
- I want eyes on everyone
- Female aged 10.
- coming and going. Be systematic.
- Brown hair, blue eyes.
Every room. Every floor. Go.
Frankie, I need you to look at
the security footage for the last hour.
Lopez, I want radio cars along Route 25,
and issue an Amber Alert.
Harbor's not far.
Kid could have fallen in.
Yeah, call the Marine Unit.
- Tell them to get a boat out there.
- [CELLPHONE BUZZES]
Evans.
Hey, uh, Chief, I'm...
I'm still at the crash site,
and, uh... NTSB is here?
Yeah, I know. I'm aware of that, Chris.
Yeah, no, no. It's... It's, uh...
It's kind of a different NTSB.
And nobody knows who
those first guys were.
[KEYS CLACKING]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Come on!
God, you got to be kidding me.
[KEYS CLACK, SPUTTERING STOPS]
♪♪
- [HEARTBEAT POUNDING]
- What?
[ENGINE STARTS, SIREN CHIRPS]
- Don't be mad.
- [GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
[DOOR OPENS]
- JO: Get in.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
We'll get you to bed,
and we'll figure everything
out tomorrow, okay?
Hey, pal.
Dad, you shouldn't have stayed up.
Eh, you know I don't sleep.
How'd it go? Oh.
Hello.
[SIGHS] We have a guest.
I see that.
[SIGHS]
Alright, let's get you to bed, okay?
I'm not tired.
Okay, well, we're gonna...
try anyway, okay?
Let's try to see if we
can find you some PJs.
♪♪
Who the hell runs around
impersonating NTSB?
You think she was on the plane?
I don't know.
Abby didn't think so. I-I don't know.
She belongs to somebody.
Gonna have to report her to
Family Services in the morning.
Yeah, I mean,
I know that's the protocol,
but if I put her in the system,
then whoever's looking for her
is gonna be able to find her.
So, what are you gonna do?
Keep a kid you just found?
- [SCOFFS]
- For how long?
- A-And what's the plan here?
- I don't have a plan. Dad, I...
I-I didn't know what else to do.
[SIGHS]
Well, you did the only
thing you could do.
- Or I kidnapped a kid.
- No. No.
She's safe. You're safe.
That's what's important.
We'll figure it out in the morning.
- Come on, honey.
- Yeah.
♪♪
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[SIGHS]
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
Okay, would you rather
be a unicorn or a wizard?
GIRL: Unicorn.
Obviously.
Would you rather have no
thumbs or only thumbs?
- Morning.
- Hey.
So, what's, uh...
What's everybody doing, huh?
Oh, Mom, okay...
What do you like better...
Ariana or Millie?
What are we talking about?
She needs a name.
Well, honey,
I imagine that she already has one.
She can't remember,
and we have to call her something.
[SEA GULL SQUAWKS IN DISTANCE]
Well, what name do you like?
I can't decide. [CHUCKLES]
You know what I always liked?
Piper. That was almost your name.
I like that one.
MIA: I love it.
I kind of love it more
than my name, but whatever.
- Well, life is hard, kid.
- [CHUCKLES]
I've got to meet Whitaker before class.
- Mom, we got to go.
- Okay.
See you later, Piper.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
- Hey, Dad, um...
- Mm-hmm?
Chris called,
and he said the NTSB's
cleared out already,
- which doesn't make any sense.
- Yeah.
So I need to go back to the site.
Okay.
You think that you guys will be...
you know...
Oh, yeah, yeah. We'll be okay.
I got a lot of projects to do today.
Could really use a helper.
Okay.
Thattagirl.
♪♪
- [PLATES CLACKING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
Um, hey, Dad?
Listen. I'll be fine.
I'll be fine. I'm feeling good.
Doc said I need to resume
normal activities, so...
No, no, I know.
I'm just... I'm saying, um...
♪♪
You know, maybe just...
stay near the house.
Or in... in... in the house.
Alright.
Okay.
And, um...
- MIA: Mom, we got to go!
- Yeah. I'm coming.
Um, Chris knows she's here,
so just call him or call me.
Okay?
- Alright.
- I'm gonna go.
Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye.
You're being really sweet with her,
and I think it helps, so thank you.
It's easy. She's cute.
Yeah, well, she's not gonna be
crashing with us for very long, so...
I don't mind.
It's, like, the only way
I'll get a little sister
now that you and Dad aren't together.
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
♪♪
[HORN HONKS]
Mom! Hurry up!
ED: This one, I take in the morning.
Uh, but it makes me thirsty.
These make hair grow all over me.
Kind of psyched about that
'cause I always wanted to be a werewolf.
[HOWLS]
Why do you take all these?
Well, uh, I used to be a firefighter,
and I was around a lot
of bad stuff that burned.
And I got something called cancer.
These are making me better.
No, they're not.
♪♪
O-kay.
[GLASS THUDS]
So, I don't suppose you know
how to install a garbage
disposal, do you?
No.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
Now, this here...
A socket wrench.
There's one about your size.
Oh, this... this is a needle-nose plier.
And my Allen wrench
must be in the basement.
I'll be right back.
Don't start without me.
[SOCKET WRENCH CLICKS]
[STATIC CRACKLING]
♪♪
[CRACKLING CONTINUES]
[CRACKLING INTENSIFIES]
♪♪
Piper.
Piper?
Ah.
[TV CHATTER]
Did you forget your new name already?
Oh. I didn't hear you.
Sorry.
Well, that's okay.
[TV SHUTS OFF]
[REMOTE THUDS]
Alright, you have my tools?
Oh, no, there they are.
Alright, let's get to work, little girl.
♪♪
[TOOLS CLACK]
[SEA GULLS SQUAWKING]
JO: Excuse me.
Are you NTSB?
[BRITISH ACCENT] Me? Oh, no.
Yikes. Definitely not.
Well, who are you?
I'm Benny.
Sir, come up here and show
me some identification.
- Now.
- Okay. Sure.
Here you go.
Oh, that's my business card.
And, uh, there's my ID.
_
You can't be here.
This is a restricted area.
Not so much anymore.
The National Transportation
Safety Board's
so-called investigation is complete.
And they cleaned it all
up for you to be helpful.
Nah, I'm kidding.
That's not what they did.
It is super weird.
Get out of here, Mr. Gallagher.
I know what the report's gonna say.
They're gonna say it
was an unmanned drone
monitoring pollution, mapping forests.
Some rubbish like that.
How do you know that?
I have sources.
Sources that you don't have.
You and I can share information.
I doubt very much
that you have any
information that I want.
What about where the
plane took off from?
♪♪
It took off from Plum Island,
about three miles off
the tip of the North Fork.
You know what's on that island?
Everyone knows what's on that island.
- Homeland Secur...
- Homeland Security research facility.
Boom. That's weird.
Do you have proof?
Not yet. But I'm right.
Okay.
Cool story.
You know, usually,
local law enforcement really likes me.
Just this thing that kind of happens.
We're laying the foundations
for a perfect working relationship.
Gonna be great!
- Hey.
- Hi.
ED: Grab a plate.
- Spaghetti and meatballs.
- Sorry, Alex.
I meant to call you and tell
you that we had company.
Well, Mia explained it.
She also said she's gonna
stay here for the weekend.
Wait, what?
I just decided I'm not leaving.
It's way too traumatic for Piper.
Oh, it's... it's too traumatic?
Um, yeah.
She needs security and consistency,
which is what all children need,
which I learned from my therapist,
so you should be so psyched about that.
This is the first I've heard of this.
And Dad's totally fine with it.
Well, we have a schedule for a reason,
sweetheart.
Okay, but you're absolutely right.
It is important that all of us
- are comfortable with the arrangement.
- Okay.
How about this, alright?
Next school break,
Dad's gonna take my days.
You guys can go fishing?
Sounds like a plan.
You're gonna love fishing.
Stick around for dinner, Alex.
Made that garlic bread you like.
Ed, thanks, but I'm good.
Hey, come here.
- Ohh! Yes!
- MIA: Ohh! [LAUGHS]
That's a tight one. I love you.
- I love you, too.
- I'll see you later.
Hey, listen, I'm really sorry, honestly.
I didn't know that
she was planning that.
I don't understand why we
have a custody schedule
if we're gonna break
it after two months.
If you really feel strongly about it,
I will tell her that
she has to go with you.
- It's fine.
- No. Don't...
No, I want to be flexible.
[SIGHS] What's going on?
You fostering this kid or something?
No, I'm keeping her here...
temporarily.
Unofficially.
She's all alone.
I mean, I couldn't just abandon her.
Okay.
It all makes sense now.
- Anybody would have done this.
- Oh, if you say so.
And it's temporary, anyway.
So temporary that Mia thinks
I'm taking them both fishing next month.
Well, who doesn't like fishing?
- I mean, you hate it.
- I know.
I feel bad for the worm.
I know.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Okay.
[SEA GULLS SQUAWKING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey.
Got everything you need?
Yep.
You know, this used to be mine.
And then I gave it to Mia.
But she's too big for it now.
She let me borrow this, too.
Wow! That is one of her favorites.
She must really like you.
So, how did things go today?
Did you...
start to remember anything?
Would you rather have hands for feet
or feet for hands?
Hmm.
Hands for feet.
- Me, too.
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
[INHALES SHARPLY, SIGHS]
Do you think maybe...
that you're afraid of remembering?
I don't know.
Hmm.
I mean, I would be,
you know, 'cause you don't know.
Could be...
sad or scary.
Maybe I won't remember ever.
Maybe. Yeah.
You know, um...
♪♪
Something really sad happened to me
when I was about your age.
What?
Well, um...
I got up one day for school, and...
... my mom was gone.
And...
she left a note
saying she was going on a trip.
But...
... she never...
She never came back.
That's so sad.
Yeah.
It was. It was really sad.
♪♪
[SNIFFLES] And you know what?
For a really long time,
I didn't want to talk about it,
and I didn't even want
to think about it.
But that...
didn't even make me feel any better.
Why?
I think sometimes...
it helps to talk about
things that are scary or sad
because then we know
that we're not alone.
If I remember, then I have to go away.
And I want to stay.
♪♪
Hmm.
Yeah.
Well, you know,
I can pretty much guarantee
that Mia's gonna want that back.
So I don't think you're
getting rid of us anytime soon.
Okay?
Okay.
♪♪
Yeah, it's, um, getting late,
so I think you should
probably get to bed, okay?
[CELLPHONE BUZZES]
Hey, Chris. What's up?
Hey, uh, you better get in here.
Something wrong?
No, I'm actually calling
with some good news.
There's a man and a woman in here,
and they say they're the girl's parents.
♪♪
Uh, so, names are
Freddie and Caitlyn Martin.
Daughter, Olivia, went missing
at the campsite last night.
Uh, did you not, uh, bring the kid?
Why don't you get them some coffee?
Okay, Chris?
Sure. Sure. Sure thing.
Mr. and Mrs. Martin?
- Hi.
- Is Olivia alright?
No one will tell us anything.
- I think we've got good news for you.
- [SIGHS]
- Oh, thank God.
Thank you, Chief Evans.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah...
We, um... We... We figured
you'd want to see some identification.
- Yeah.
- We only have her passport with us,
but we have her birth
certificate at home...
Whatever you need.
That's okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Wow. Charlotte.
What brings you guys up to Long Island?
I grew up nearby,
so we came to do some camping.
Can we see Olivia?
Mid-week camping?
Middle of the school year?
Lucky kid. [CHUCKLES]
How did you guys get separated?
She was in the tent
when we went to sleep.
- Mm-hmm.
- But, uh...
when we woke up, she was just gone.
And we tried calling 911,
but we couldn't get through.
So we just... We drove here.
I know you must think
we are terrible parents.
No, I don't think that.
Honestly, kids...
You know, they wander off.
I wish you guys had called sooner.
Like I said, we tried,
but there was no signal out there.
I mean, I...
Look, I still don't have one.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. How is the camera on that?
It's fine. It's just like
a regular camera.
I mean, I only ever take
pictures on my phone anymore,
and my phone is just like
90% pictures of my kid.
I'm sure yours is the same way.
Do you mind if I...
I'm thinking about getting a new one.
I just want to...
Can I see your pictures of Olivia?
♪♪
We've answered your questions.
I'd like to see my daughter.
Now.
Of course.
I apologize.
I... I'll be right back.
[INHALES SHARPLY] You know what?
And I will, um, warm
those up for you, too.
Sorry about that.
Okay.
Don't touch the sides.
Pull prints. Run them immediately.
Wait, what ha... what happened?
They are not who they say they are.
- They... They had passports.
- They had passp...
[ELECTRICITY HUMS, ELECTRONICS WHIRRING]
♪♪
- _
- [CELLPHONE BUZZES]
What's wrong?
I need you to go over
to the house, okay,
and... and...
And get Mia and Dad and Piper.
Yo. What the hell is going on?
Alex, can you do this or not?
Where do you want me to take them?
Go to the place
where we set the kitchen on fire.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Just say yes or no.
- Yeah. Jo...
- Do not bring your cellphone.
What?
I-I'll be there as soon as I can.
[CLICK]
- ALEX: See?
- [METAL CLACKS]
How much fun is this?
Right? So much fun!
It's like we're camping!
Well, but we're inside.
Yeah, I love middle-of-the-night
beach trips on a school night.
ED: Got some hot-chocolate
fixings in there.
- Who wants some?
- Grandpa, seriously?
Hot chocolate?
[VEHICLE APPROACHES]
I would like some.
Well, I mean, yeah. So would I.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
It's her.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Hey, honey.
- Hey, Dad.
Hey, Mom.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Ooh!
- [LOCK CLICKS]
- Wow. Looks so fun in here.
Oh!
We're having hot chocolate.
Oh, that sounds great.
I'll have some of that, too.
- Hey, um, um...
- Jo.
it's... this is a prepaid,
just, you know,
so you have it if you need it.
[EXHALES FORCEFULLY]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
Well, I suppose you're all wondering
why I've called you here today.
Jo. It's not funny.
I'm sorry.
Hmm.
Okay [CLEARS THROAT] um...
So...
tonight, two people came by the station,
and they said that they
were Piper's parents.
But they were lying.
I don't know... who they are.
I don't know why
they're looking for you.
But I'm gonna find out, okay?
Listen to me.
I am not gonna let them take you.
Alright?
I'm gonna keep you safe.
Why do they want to take me?
You know, I don't know.
But, I bet the answer
is right in here, somewhere.
We all gonna sleep in this room tonight?
ED: Sure. Safety in numbers.
Uh, I got a couple of cots
in the hallway closet.
Do you want to help me with them?
JO: Yeah.
I'll try to remember.
What?
I'll try really hard.
I know. It's okay.
♪♪
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to pull you into this.
I'm worried, Jo.
No, it's okay.
We're gonna be okay. It's fine.
That's not why I'm worried.
I'm worried because either
something's really messed up
or you're really paranoid.
I see. So I'm crazy.
That's a good explanation for you.
Well, Jo, you're not giving me one.
All I see is you pulling
people out of bed
in the middle of the night
and buying me a damn burner phone.
A plane crashed on the beach, alright,
and then was cleaned up
pretty much instantaneously.
I found a kid at the crash site
I'm being told wasn't even on the plane.
Fake federal agents.
Fake parents that just vanish?
I wish I was being paranoid.
Alex, I don't think that I am.
And don't tell... don't tell me
that I'm putting my family in danger.
I'm not saying that.
I didn't know what else to do.
I'm not saying that, okay?
I'm not saying that. I'm here.
I'm here to help.
Thank you.
[SOFT THUD]
MIA: Mom, what was that?
Mom!
♪♪
What... W-What was that?
Shh. Shh. Okay? Shh.
[FLOORBOARDS CREAKING]
Somebody's out there.
♪♪
[DOORKNOB RATTLES]
[WHISPERING] Right here.
♪♪
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
[FOOTSTEPS, GLASS CRUNCHING]
♪♪
Go, go, go.
- [SHOES SQUEAKING]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[PIPER PANTING, WHIMPERING]
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
Come on.
- Stay down.
- [WHIMPERS]
ED: Get a blanket.
Stand back. Cover your eyes.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Two, three.
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [SCREAMS]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Police! I'm armed!
- [ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
- MAN: Now!
♪♪
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[WHIMPERS]
♪♪
Mom, what's happening?!
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
Let's go! Let's go!
ALEX: Come on!
Okay. Alex, you first.
Alright. Come on.
- ED: Let's go. Let's go.
- Hi.
- Go on. Go, go, go, go, go.
- Sweetie. Sweetie, you're next.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
Dad, you're next.
Like hell.
[GRUNTS]
- MIA: Mom! Come quick!
- Come on.
I'm good. Go. Go.
[ALEX GRUNTS]
- JO: What happened?
- I'm alright.
- Someone hit me.
- Where's Piper?
- [ENGINE REVS]
- Mom, you have to go get her!
- Piper!
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- [RADIO CHIRPS, SIREN WAILING]
- Dispatch, this is Evans.
OPERATOR: Go ahead, Chief.
Child abduction in progress.
I need all available
units to the utility road
parallel to County Road 48.
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- Copy, Chief.
All available units,
support for the utility road
parallel to County Road 48.
Child abduction in progress. Officers...
[WAILING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[PANTING]
♪♪
[STEAM HISSING]
[GLASS SCRAPES]
♪♪
[PIPER GROANS]
JO: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay. I got you.
- [WHIMPERS]
- You okay?
- Are you okay?
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
Are you... Are you hurt?
Are you hurt?
[PANTING]
♪♪
H... How?
I-I don't know.
It's okay. It's okay.
♪♪
CHRIS: Freddie and
Caitlyn Martin's identities
were fakes.
And the prints were not in the system.
I could run their DNA
through the database,
but I'm... I'm pretty sure
that's a dead end, too.
Uh, this was found on the guy.
What is it?
Uh, nobody can figure that out.
Uh, no... no circuitry, no...
nothing magnetic.
And, um, NTSB reached out,
said that plane wasn't a plane at all.
Uh, unmanned drone.
The National Science Foundation
mapping forest coverage.
I mean, I-I don't want to sound crazy,
but, um...
they're lying to us, right?
I mean, you don't sound crazy.
What is going on?
I don't know.
I think it has something
to do with Piper, though.
Who... Who's Piper?
Oh, Piper is the kid we found.
Mia kind of... gave her a name.
Um...
I'm, uh... [SIGHS]
I'm not putting her in the system.
I'm keeping her with me.
Which is...
very much not legal.
♪♪
And I'm gonna ask you to do
something equally illegal
and keep it to yourself.
Done. Easy.
Don't... Don't even worry about it.
Thanks, Chris.
JO: Hi, there. [SIGHS]
BENNY: How'd you find me?
Oh, I have sources, too.
Also, I've had a tail on
you since we first met.
Thanks, Frankie.
No problem, Chief.
BENNY: [CHUCKLES]
Well played. Oyster?
Listen, under normal circumstances,
I would never trust you.
But right now,
I don't know who I can trust.
That's an excellent policy.
I did find out that the
phony government agents
recovered and removed the black box
and human remains from the crash site.
Does that change your
opinion of me at all?
What are you waiting for?
You're a reporter.
Why don't you report this?
Nah.
You never write it until
you have the whole story.
Maybe you can find out what this is.
I'll let you know.
[KEYS CLACK]
Alright.
I see how it is.
I go to work,
and you steal my jacket and my bed.
Mia said it was more comfortable.
Oh, okay.
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
You okay?
Oh.
Those people... They're gone forever.
Okay?
And they can't ever get to you again.
I know.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
Do you think I crashed that plane?
No.
I don't.
I don't think that at all.
♪♪
Well, I am gonna go get changed.
And as for you...
I bought you a toothbrush.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Go brush.
♪♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WATER RUNNING]
[SPITS]
[WATER TRICKLING, ECHOING]
♪♪
[WATER GURGLING]
[WATER RUNNING]
[BILLIE EILISH'S
"YOU SHOULD SEE ME IN A CROWN" PLAYS]
♪ Bite my tongue, bide my time ♪
♪ Wearing a warning sign ♪
♪ Wait till the world is mine ♪
♪ Count my cards, watch them fall ♪
♪ Blood on a marble wall ♪
♪ I like the way they a-a-a-all ♪
♪ Scream ♪
♪ Tell me which one is worse ♪
♪ Living or dying first ♪
♪ Sleeping inside a hearse ♪
♪ I don't dream ♪
♪ I'm okay ♪
♪ I'm not your baby ♪
♪ If you think I'm pretty ♪
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ I'm gonna run this nothing town ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow ♪
♪ One by, one by ♪
♪ One ♪
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ Your silence is my favorite sound ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow one by one ♪
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com