No, we were gonna end this, Sam.
Like you said.
We're gonna be free.
To perform this spell,
I have to die.
It has to be you
that kills me.
You didn't have a choice.
I'm pissed.
I'll be damned if I'm gonna let
some glorified fanboy
get the last word.
Oh, no.
Oh, Becky.
I am your number-one fan.
I'm samlicker81.
So you dosed me
with love potion.
It wasn't all bad, right?
Uh, Becky, would you excuse us
for just a second?
Uh-huh.
Amara,
we belong together.
You're not complete.
You're not at full strength.
You can't
leave this world.
You're trapped, diminished,
abandoned.
♪♪
Next to me.
Back up! Back up!
♪♪
Benny?
Dean.
Hey.
Dean.Hey, you're gonna be okay.
Naw...
I'm not.
I...
I'll see you on the other side,
brother.
♪♪
Benny...
Benny.
♪♪
Where is he?
He's closer than you think.
Where?!
Maybe I'll tell you.
Right before
I rip out your --
♪♪
He was right.
Closer than you think.
Sam?
You know, I knew
you'd come looking for me.
After Sioux Falls...
I suppose you had to.
What you did to them...
what you did to Bobby...
to Jody...
They tried to stop me.
But I will not
be stopped.
Sam, you listen to me.
This is
the demon blood.
You have to fight it!
Why would I do that?
♪♪
Sammy, please...
Please.
♪♪
Morning.
Rough night?
Yeah, just, uh...
weird dreams.
Yeah, been there.
Why don't you eat something?
You'll feel better.
Dean, you know
I don't eat --
It's veggie bacon.
What? You've been asking for it.
Yeah. But every time
I ask for it, you say,
and I'm quoting, "I don't want
any of that hippie,
Sarah McLaughlin
grass-eater crap
in the Meat Man's
kitchen."
Which, by the way,
for what it's worth,
you got to stop calling yourself
"The Meat Man."
It -- It doesn't mean
what you think it means.
Yeah, it does.
Anyway, it's not that bad.
Give it a shot.
I'm good.
No, you're not.
The past few days, you've barely
come outta your room.
Look, man,
I get it, okay?
With Jack...
and Rowena...
♪♪
Rowena knew what she was
getting herself into.
She knew
what needed to be done.
Doesn't make it
any easier.
No, it doesn't.
♪♪
Here.
In the last month,
Beaverdale, Iowa,
has seen more than a half-dozen
cattle mutilations.
So, what, mountain lion,
or --
Mm. Three days ago,
a girl's body showed up --
ripped to pieces.
Now, local badges think
they've got themselves
a psycho on their hands,
but, I mean,
come on, man, that sounds
exactly like our thing.
So let's go
check it out.
You know, Dean, you can
handle this on your own,
or -- or call up
some of the other hunters --
No, no.
You and me.
Sam, we need this.
That -- That's real bacon, Dean.
You're damn right it is.
Meat Man!
♪♪
Yeah, watch the bikes.
Davis, use a crosswalk.
Let's go!
Keep it moving!
So...
...our victim...
Susie Martin.
Yeah.
What happened to her,
I can't even imagine.
The police said
she was last seen here.
After cheer practice.
And the, uh,
security cameras?
Uh, the police checked
but nothing.
Was she close to anyone?
Susie was close
to everyone.
She was part of the drama club,
debate team,
cheerleading, campus ministry --
you name it.
Any best friends?
Mostly Veronica
and the girls.
They're putting together
a prayer vigil for her.
Excuse me, Mrs. Bailey?
Oh, Mr. And Mrs. Whitman,
how can I help you?
Well, it's just --
we heard a rumor
that the game is gonna be
cancelled this Friday?
Oh, not canceled, rescheduled --
for the service.
For Susie.Right. And we're so sorry
about what happened to her.
I mean, it's just
so, so horrible, but...
Uh, we had a scout coming to
that game for Billy --
from Yale.
A young lady is dead, and you're
worried about a football game?
It's lacrosse.
Who are you?
Agent Plant, FBI.
Oh.
It's just, Yale's
Billy's first choice,
and if he doesn't get in,
it'll be the end of the world.
Actually, the end of the world
is the end of the world.
Of course.Of course.
But maybe you could
have the --
the little prayer thing
at halftime?
Or --
No.
Well, is --
I see.
Well...
thank you for your time.
I swear, the parents
are worse than the kids.
Hey.
Any luck at the morgue?
Is that a...?
Vamp fang.
Vampires
drain their victims.
Vamps don't
rip their bodies apart.
Apparently, this one does.
And it gets a little weirder.
Coroner said that there were
no sign of defensive wounds,
so it's like
she didn't even fight.
So whoever killed her,
maybe it was someone she knew.
And according to
the vice principal,
she kind of knew everyone.
Oh, that's awesome.
♪♪
That's awesome.
Ha!
You see that beaver?
I know. Cheer practice
was so long, right?
I swear, Veronica's so fake.
"I'm lost without Susie.
It's like a piece of my heart
is gone."
Gag me.
Okay, yeah. Later.
♪♪
So, this is where
they found Susie's body?
Yeah.
You notice what's missing?
Blood.
So, how does a freak gut a girl
and not make a mess?
By killing her somewhere else
and dumping her here.
Looks like.
Yeah. Great.
Well,
local police are freaked.
Never seen anything like this.
They got no idea how to deal.
Of course not.
That's our job.
We keep them from
dealing with the truth,
with what's out there,
and we carry the weight.
It's great.
Meanwhile, they get to
go back to living in
their white picket fence
bubbles.
You know,
ever since you were a kid,
you wanted to live
in a town like this.
Lame, normal...
Yeah,
we don't get normal.
And these towns, everything's
the end of the world.
You're late for work,
your kid doesn't get into
the right school -- whatever.
They don't...
They have no idea
what's out there.
Huh.
Vice Principal
Bailey?
Yes.
Really?
Of course,
uh, on our way.
We got another one.
♪♪
Seat belts, seat belts.
Okay.
We know, Dad.
Got this, got that,
got that.
You're forgetting
something.
Motion-sickness pills --
for Junior.
He would've been fine, babe.
It's just Lake Michigan.
Hardly any chop.Four hours in a boat?
Rod Jr. Gets seasick
in the tub.
Where would I be
without you?
Covered in puke.
Have fun, sweeties!
Thanks, Mom, we will.
Wow.
Felt that.
You can't wait to
have the house to yourself.
Oh, you have no idea.
- Bye, Mom!
- Bye!
Bye, Mom!
♪♪
Becky, wait!
Becky, please.
Becky, please wait.
What are you doing here?
I just -- I wanted to --
I needed to see you.
Well, I don't want
or need to see you.
I'm sorry, I --
I know we're not together
anymore,
and it seems like
you're doing great.
I just -- I --
I wanted to talk.
Catch up.
It's been a rough
couple of weeks.
That's not my problem.
Wait, Becky, please.
I don't have
anywhere else to go.
Tori Taylor
never came home last night.
She was talking to a friend
on the phone,
in the parking lot,
and then... gone.
What about her vehicle?
It's still there,
which is --
Not good.
Her parents are worried sick.
They --
Do you think
she and Susie --Let's start with this.
The girls, did they have
anything in common?
They're both
cheerleaders.
Well,
somebody's got a fetish.
Excuse me?
I, uh --
We'll look into it.
What are these?
My maquettes.
You... make them?
I run the most successful
Etsy site
for unofficial "Supernatural"
merchandise in the country.
Probably the world.
Wow.
So you're still, um...
Still what?
Uh,
obsessed with my work.
You mean my work.
Look, what you were writing,
it was real --
like, really real.
You sort of channeled
Sam and Dean's lives
because you're a prophet.
I... Yeah.
Yes, I am.
And, sure,
I got a little obsessed,
and it took me
to a dark place.
What I did to Sam...
So, after some pretty intensive
counseling,
I realized I wasn't in love
with the real Sam Winchester.
I loved his character.
So instead of
reading your stories,
I kept writing my own.
Your own...
"Supernatural"?
Where the guys didn't have to
hunt monsters all the time.
They just sit around and
do laundry and talk, you know?
I mean, that's what people like
the most, anyway.
Well, I mean,
people like monsters.
Meh.
Anyway,
I got an online following,
and it wasn't
paying the bills,
so I started to make these
handcrafted miniatures.
They took off, started turning
a profit, and here I am.
Right. Right, right,
right, right, right.
But people like monsters,
though. They do.
I mean,
leviathans are cool.
What?
They're all teeth!
Anyway, I have the house
to myself
for the first time
in months.
This was supposed to be
my catch-up day.
I have billing to do,
orders to fill,
three AU Fic deadlines
breathing down my neck.
So if you want to talk,
talk.
Fast.
Like, there's -- Like,
they don't even have lips.
They're just,
like, teeth face.
Raa--
Chuck!
Okay.
Now.
All right. Fine.
All right, so I had
a bit of a falling out.
With who?
The Winchesters?
Things were said.
Uh...
Now I've found myself
low on, um...
resources.
I went to ask my sister
for help,
and she rejected me.
'Cause she sucks.
And now I'm just...
stuck.
So I thought
I'd come see you,
my number-one fan.
And, I don't know, see if you
can help make me feel big again.
So, you want me to...
fluff you?
W--
I mean, no.
You do.
You thought you could just
come back to me,
your pathetic ex,
your number-one fan,
and get what you've always
gotten from me --
a nice big crank
on your ego.
Well, I mean --
Well, sorry, that's not me
anymore, Chuck.
I am married
to an amazing man,
I have two great kids,
and I like myself,
Chuck.
For the first time
in a long time,
I like myself.
So I don't need you.
I know.
You don't need me.
No one does.
I'm happy for you Becky,
that you like yourself.
Because...
I kind of hate me
right now.
♪♪
Really?
Yeah, I just don't know
what I'm doing.
I feel so lost.
Okay. Well...
What makes you happy?
Writing.
Creating.
Then, Chuck,
you have to write.
♪♪
Really?
You're sure?
Okay, all right.
Thanks, Toby.
Appreciate it.
Seriously?
We're questioning
mascots now?
Smart kid.
He's actually got
a full ride to IU.
Don't underestimate the mascot,
man.
The guy's got access.
He knows a lot
about cheerleaders.
In a mostly-non-creepy
kind of way.
Anyway, so, turns out
Susie was in charge.
Then with her gone, Tori was
set to take over, except...
Not anymore.
Yeah.
Okay. So, who's third in line
to the throne?
Mm.
Not the mascot,
but he knows.
♪♪
I can't believe
she's really...
I know.
It's just...
It's like a piece of my heart
is gone.
Billy, I know
you and Susie were close,
but if there's anything
you need...
♪♪
I...
Billy!
♪♪
I have to go.
Yeah.
♪♪
All right.
We are here to celebrate
the life of my friend, Susie --
No.
We are here to celebrate the
life of my best friend, Susie --
my best friend, Susie,
who I miss like --
like she was a part of me.
And in many ways,
she is still a part of me.
She'll always be
a part of all of us.
Susie Martin was
as rare as a ghost orchid
and as unique as a snowflake.
So beautiful inside and out.
But as Robert Frost tells us,
"Nothing gold can stay."
And that's what Susie was --
pure gold.
That's good stuff.
Especially the part
about the snowflake,
and, uh,
getting choked up.
I mean,
if you're gonna milk it,
really get in there
and squeeze, you know?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
FBI.
We're here about Susie.
Uh, you mean
about who killed her?
Yeah.
Yeah, now that she's gone
and then Tori,
really kind of worked out
for you, didn't it?
We should talk.
Outside.
Um, I --
I think I should go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Veronica...
do you have braces?
♪♪
Yeah. So?
Friggin' braces?
Kinda makes it impossible
to fang out.
All right, so if she's not
our vamp, then who is?
♪♪
You weren't out front.
I had to find you.
It was embarrassing, Mom.
I just wanted to help.
Susie would have want--No.
We do not say her name.
Would you talk to your son,
please?
Just listen
to your mother.
Really?
I need wine.
♪♪
You have anything stronger?
We have
cran-apple juice.
Hmm.
I'm good.
It's just, things are
different now, Becky.
I mean, I used to be able to see
Sam and Dean in my head,
wherever they were,
whatever they were doing.
It was all just there,
ripe for the picking.
And now it's just gone.
Because you lost
your prophet powers?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Then write about
something else.
But this it. I mean,
this is my favorite story.
Then write about them.
I-I -- Okay.
I feel like we're going
in circles now.
No,
you'regoing in circles.
You're a writer,
a writer who's not writing.
And when a writer's
not writing,
they feel sad,
and they get lost.
And the writer
asks themselves,
"Why do I feel this way?
Why am I
so sad and lost?"
And what does
all this navel-gazing
and hair-pulling
amount to in the end?
Procrastination,
distraction.
Just one of a million ways
the writer avoids
doing the one thing that is
all but guaranteed
to make the writer
feel better.
Which is...?
Writing.
But what if I can't?
You can.
The only question is,
will you?
How'd you learn all this?
I'm a writer, too,
Chuck.
Oh. I mean, fanfic -- it's not
really the same thing --
Writing's writing.
Okay.
The self-sabotage,
the doubts,
the struggle against time.
So whenever I have
a spare minute,
I write.
♪♪
Yeah.
Yeah!
♪♪
Wait.
I didn't mean right now --
Shh, shh, shh!
♪♪
This is the security
footage from last night.
Do we have any idea
who that might be?
No clue.
He's wearing a mask.
Well, crap.
Wait a second.
Go back.
Uh, zoom into that.
You got it?
Yeah.
You're worried about the game?
I mean, this is insane!
This is what
we've been worked for,
what we've sacrificed
so much for.
Well,
I never asked you to.
We're your parents.
You don't need to ask.
Everything that we have done
has been for you.
We just want you to
be happy.
Son,
we're trying our best.
W-What do you
want from us?
Listen to what I'm saying --
I don't want anything.
I never wanted any of this!
That's the point!
Hi.
Your dad home?
Uh, Dad?
♪♪
Billy, get upstairs.
Now.
♪♪
Good thinking.
You don't want the kid
to see this part.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yeah, sure you do.
Those girls
that went missing...
that was you.
♪♪
On it.
Look, arrest me.
Fine.
Just -- Just please
leave my family out of it.
♪♪
Arrest you?
No, see?
We're not FBI.
Shh.
I'm here to help, okay?
Just hang in there.
Hang in there.
And we know exactly
what you are.
♪♪
I'm gonna get you out of here,
okay?
I got you.
You shouldn't be here.
Sammy, how's it going
back there?!
♪♪
Okay.
Was not expecting that.
How's she doing?
Not good.
She's lost
a lot of blood.
She needs a doctor.
Janet,
what are you doing?
I'm saving this family.
No. Listen.
It's over, okay?
They --
They caught me.
You just need to get Billy
and leave.
♪♪
Please.
Well?
It's so good!
You did it.
Congratulations!
Yeah?
I mean, the story --
I loved it.
In fact, I'm feeling
so inspired,
I would love to just jump in
and get back to my own work.
No, no, no,
you're shining me on.
What?
No, I'm not --
It's a rough draft,
Becky.
You've gotta
have some notes.
Just, like, one note.
Okay.
If I had to give
one note...
The jeopardy, Chuck --
it's feeling a little...
thin?
Low-stakes?
It's fun to hear the boys'
voices,
but a story is only
as good as its villain,
and these villains are just not
feeling very... dangerous?
Not to mention,
there's no classic rock.
No one
even mentions Cass.
The climax
is a little stale.
Boys tied up again while we get
the villains' monologue,
which, frankly,
isn't one of your best.
A little originality
wouldn't...
♪♪
...hurt.
You want jeopardy?
You want danger?
♪♪
Move!
I'll give you danger.
♪♪
Chuck?
Chuck!
Dad, what's going...
on...
Your dad's a vampire.
That's what's going on.
Let me guess -- few weeks ago,
maybe a month,
you had a run-in with
something big and mean.
It turned you.
You thought you could deal.
But the cow's blood or whatever
just wasn't cutting it,
so you upgraded to humans.
How am I doing?
Am I right?
No, I don't think you're right,
Dean.
♪♪
It's not the dad,
it's the son.
Shut your mouth! Mom --
Billy, go!
No.
You're right,
about all of it.
Okay? But what happened
with Susie, I didn't --
♪♪
We were together.
We were kissing...
I could hear her heart...
And her blood, and she --
it just tasted so good,
I just...
♪♪
I couldn't stop.
Then what?
I told my mom and dad.
♪♪
So, you, what --
chopped up the body?
Made it look like
some wannabe Bundy?
And then grabbed Tori
and...
...and kept her as
his own personal blood bag?
Awesome parenting.
Awesome.
This is not
Billy's fault.
He was the victim.
What were we
supposed to do?
You were gonna let me
just cut off your head.
You don't have children,
do you?
Because if you did,
you would know
that to see your child in pain
rips your heart out.
And you'd know that
you'd do anything.
You'd die for them.
Or kill for them.
Mom, no.
We can bury them out back,
under the peonies.
Everything
is going to be fine.
There's no way
you believe that.
♪♪
Mom...
Stop.
♪♪
We just wanted him to have
a normal life.
♪♪
Mom, I can't.
That's what I've been trying
to tell you.
I can't.
I killed someone that I loved,
and I'll do it again.
I know I will.
I can't control this!
♪♪
I'm a monster.
So here's
what's gonna happen.
You're gonna take Tori
to the hospital,
and you're gonna tell them
that I kidnapped her.
What? No.
Dad said he was wearing a mask
when he grabbed her.
Tori won't know.
You tell them I took her...
and then I ran away.
Billy, don't do this.
♪♪
Then you and me...
we're gonna
go for a ride.
That's how this works...
right?
♪♪
I'm sorry, Mom.
But this is the best way.
This is the only way.
♪ Finding room to breathe
♪ Go on beyond your way
♪ And see
♪ And though
♪ The sounds of someday
♪ May be home
♪ And though
♪ The sounds of someday
♪ May be home
♪ Yeah
♪♪
No.
You can't --
I did.
Y--
This is just an ending.
Yeah.
I don't know how
I'm gonna get there,
but I know
where I'm goin'.
B-But it's so...
dark.
But great, right?
I can see it now --
"Supernatural: The End."
And the cover is just
a gravestone
that says "Winchester."
♪♪
The fans
are gonna love it.
Well?
It's awful!
Horrible.
It's hopeless.
♪♪
You can't do this
to the fans.
What you did to Dean?
What you did to Sam?
There, see?
It's making you feel something.
That's good, right?
No!
Babe!
We're home!
You have to leave.
Nah,
I kind of like it here.
Babe, you wouldn't believe
what happened.
Please.Junior was fine,
but I puked everywhere.
Babe?
Hey.
Rod?!
What happened?
Where is he?
He's gone.
What?!
- Hey, Mom, we're back!
- Hi, Mom!
Dad got sick!
He threw up all over the side
of the b--
- Dad threw u--
No!
The kids.
Oh, don't worry.
They're not dead.
They're just away.
Oh, yeah.
I'm God.
♪♪
What are you --
No.
You bring them back.
You bring them back!
♪♪
Please...
you can't do this.
Oh, Becky.
♪♪
I can do anything.
I'm a writer.
♪♪
Well, that was
an interesting one.
Yeah.
What Henry did...
we'd have done
the same thing.
For Jack.
If we had the chance.
Yeah.
Yeah, we would.
Look, man, I get it.
I get it.
We have lost way, way too much.
And it's hard not to feel like
just... cashing out.
I felt like that.
After Chuck,
back at the crypt.
But you know what
brought me back?
You did.
By sayin' that what we do
still matters.
♪♪
I mean, that's why I wanted to
drag us out here.
That's why I wanted to --
to work a case,
to save lives,
you know?
'Cause it is -- it's a --
it's a crap job.
We do the ugly things so that
people can live happy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Lucky them.
♪♪
Yeah, lucky them.
But it doesn't
change a thing.
You know what I mean?
We still do the job.
♪♪
But we don't do it for us.
We did it for Jack,
for Mom,
for Rowena.
We owe it to anybody who has
ever gave a damn about us
to keep putting one foot
in front of the other.
No matter what.
And, hey, man,
like you said,
now that Chuck's gone,
we're finally on our own.
We are finally free to...
move on, you know?
♪♪
I don't know. Uh...
I-I don't know if I can move on.
You know,
I -- I -- I --
I can't forget
any of them.
Dean, I still think
about Jessica.
I -- I can't just
let that go.
No, man, that's not
what I'm talking about.
I know, I know, I know.
I'm sorry. I know.
But -- But what I'm saying is
that I don't feel free.
♪♪
What we've done,
what we've lost, right now,
that is what I'm feeling,
and -- and sometimes it's...
♪♪
Sometimes it's like
I-I-I can't even breathe.
♪♪
But maybe tomorrow.
You know, maybe I'll --
I'll feel better in the morning.
♪♪
And what if you don't?
I don't know.
♪♪
Oh, yeah.
This is gonna be good.
♪♪